November 1942
Rastenburg East-Prussia
Sit down ladies.
One moment. The Führer is feeding
his dog. He'll see you in a short while.
Can you tell us... How are we supposed
to address the Führer?
The Führer first speaks to you
and then you reply: Heil mein Führer.
And the Nazi salute?
That won't be necessary...
since the Führer isn't looking for
a soldier but for a secretary.
Act as normal and calm
as you can.
I'll see if
he has time for you.
Mein Führer
the ladies from Berlin are here.
Thank you for coming
in the middle of the night.
Sometimes during a war
one is not in control of time.
Can I ask your name?
-Margarethe Lorenz.
Where are you from?
-From Fulda.